# EKATERINA SAVRAS

+375336451985 katerina.savras@gmail.com Linkedin: <u>in/ekaterina-savras/</u>

GitHub: katesavras

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm a Frontend Developer with more than one year of professional experience. I have experience in adaptive layout web-sites adhering to the concept of a component approach, experience with CSS preprocessors, Java Script, React, ability to use Flexible Box Layout, Grid, Bootstrap. I have developed an app using React, Redux, and Hooks. I have a creative mind and I'm ready for new challenges. I always try to do my work the best way.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML/HTML5
- CSS/SCSS
- Java Script

- React
- Redux
- Git

- Bootstrap
- Figma
- Webpack/Gulp

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022 **Senticode** Frontend Developer

- Creating adaptive web-pages for bootstrap layout using Figma, HTML5, SCSS, Bootstrap
- Learned ASP.NET Razor and migrated layout to its components

Mar 2022 - Dec 2022 Ester Dijital Frontend Developer

- Creating adaptive, cross-browser web-pages for layout using Figma, HTML5, SCSS, Bootstrap, Pixel Perfect, BEM methodology.
- Writing and implementing, clean code for components using Java Script, React.
- Experience with Vue.js.

Projects: <a href="https://ester.co/">https://www.lupovis.io/</a>

https://rsvpify.com/wedding-rsvp-response-time-calculator-2022/

#### COURSES

Oct 2020 - Sep 2021 **TeachMeSkills** Frontend Developer

- Designed and developed an app Lingvary for learning English words using react, redax, redux-thunk, hooks, scss, uuid and also eslint and prettier
- As a backend, I used the google firebase data storage <a href="https://github.com/katesavras/lingvary">https://github.com/katesavras/lingvary</a>



#### **EDUCATION**

2012 - 2018 Belarusian State Medical University Bachelor's degree

#### LANGUAGES

Russian: Native English: Intermediate